Don Alfons Nisnoni Resume

PERSONAL DATA



Date of Birth: 18 September 1995 (26 years old)

Address: Semangka street, Amnesi, Kota Raja sub-district, Kupang city,

East Nusa Tenggara, Indonesia **Phone:** +6282147747572

Preffered Position: Front-end Web Developer

Email: donalfonsnnisnoni@gmail.com

Website: donnisnoni.github.io

GitHub: donnisnoni **LinkedIn:** donnisnoni

SUMMARY

Hello!

Hi there! My name is Don Alfons Nisnoni. I'm a front-end web developer from Indonesia. I mostly do front-end web development on my daily programming activity. I learn web development since 2015 when web programming lecture is introduced to me on my campus. Since then, I falling in love with web development.

Fresh graduate

I just graduated back in november 2020 with GPA of 3.44. Actually, I finished my college on december 2019. But because of COVID-19 pandemic, the graduation ceremony is postponed.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree of Computer Science @ STIKOM UYELINDO Kupang

Jul 2015 - Dec 2019 - **GPA: 3.44** - Graduated on Nov 2020 due COVID-19

SKILLS

Thing's that I've touch so far:

Software/Tools:

Git, GitHub, Docker, Netlify, Vercel, PostCSS, Hugo SSG

Databases:

Redis, MySQL & MariaDB

Programming Languages:

HTML, CSS, Javascript, NodeJS, Typescript, C#, V, SASS, SQL, PHP

Frameworks/Libraries:

jQuery, Vue, Svelte, Sapper, Codelgniter, Laravel, Express, Fastify, Sequelize, TailwindCSS

Technique:

Responsive Web Desing, ally, i18n, PWA

EXPERIENCES

Web Developer

Feb 2020 - Aug 2020 @ STIKOM UYELINDO Kupang

- Build a website for improve student's online services
- Upgrade & improve campus main website
- Create work email for lecturer's
- Analyze and improve existing campus websites security and UI
- Upgrade campus tech stacks

Part-time Front-End Web Developer

Feb 2020 - Present @ Vlingo

• Implementing vlingo/auth UI